what's going on everybody welcome back
to another one and in this video we're
going to be doing a little bit of a
product review yet again on one of my
new bait casters and I'm very very I'm
thoroughly impressed with this thing and
I think you guys will be too it honestly
is somewhat into the budget space for
baitcasters but we're going to be
reviewing the Abu Garcia Max Pro and now
this thing honestly has met a lot of my
expectations for 120 dollars It's seems
to be a very quality piece of equipment
and we're going to talk about what I
think of it we're going to jump into it
we're out on the kayak tonight Sun's
going down it should be Prime Time
fishing we're going to talk about it
we're going to get into it so let's jump
into some fishing so we're fishing with
the Abu Garcia Max Pro today guys and
this baitcaster is a relatively budget
baitcaster coming in with a combo you
can get in a left-handed or right-handed
size this baitcaster is a left-handed
because I do like to reel left-handed
with my bait casters and it's a seven
foot medium heavy Rod which honestly
gives you plenty of backbone and more
than enough power to reel your fish in
which is very nice you know you can get
some budget bait casters where they
don't really have enough backbone and
you got to be careful about that coming
in at 120 bucks honestly it seems like a
pretty good buy I'm running 30 pound
Power Pro so far I haven't had any
problems bird net Bird's nesting we
actually might have a fish on here
I think we do no it must have been a
weed
but I haven't had any problems Birds
nesting I spent a little bit of it I
spent a little bit of time dialing it in
um but honestly just a couple casts and
I was good to go and I'm not throwing a
super heavy you know super heavy lure or
anything like that I didn't try the
weightless senko yet which I'll probably
get to that once I get it a little bit
more broken but as you can see I mean
super smooth an old bird's nest there
and this thing has eight ball bearings
so the Reel is honestly pretty much a
highlight too The Reel seems to be
pretty much pretty quality I don't think
there's really anything I would change
about the Reel just because with your
budget set up sometimes they lack
quality in the Reel but it doesn't seem
like it in this case The Reel seems to
be very good very quality oh oh we're
getting bit
oh I think we oh no we got him we got
him oh yeah we got them let's go not
super big but we'll take that all night
son well that was quite the rod flip
right there but heck yeah
just a little guy check that out right
in the top of the lip perfect perfect
hook set as you can see that it really
got the job done there which is pretty
cool but we'll send that guy back geez
thank you for that buddy getting me all
wet took my senko too but plenty of
plenty of power on your hook sets you
have plenty of drag with the Reel
um so it seems like they really didn't
shortcut The Reel at all and it seems
like the rod is pretty good I like this
handle back here
I would say though that the handle
probably could be a little bit bigger I
mean it's it does it serves its purpose
but I can't really grip my whole can't
really grip my whole hand on this thing
you know it's just kind of there for a
little bit of extra give when you want
to go for a little bit longer cast but
it works it serves its purpose you know
I can see that they maybe did you know
go a little bit cheaper on the end here
but I suppose some people probably like
that too so it's kind of all you know
preference that way but the rod does
seem to be made with Quality Parts and
obviously the white finish just looks so
cool you know I like this little like uh
texture that they have here it's not
textured but I do like the little
graphic that they put at the first you
know until the first eyelid on the rod
that looks super super nice
um the grip it's made of like a almost
like a rubbery feel which feels pretty
good in your hand I mean it's not it's
not too much of a grip but you do have a
little bit of a rib material on the
bottom here to kind of just you know
seat your fingers in which is nice I
also did want to mention if you guys
like this content make sure you
subscribe to the channel because we have
a lot more product review content coming
in the near future and it's going to be
good so make sure you subscribe let's
get back to the action one of the tests
I like to do for you guys I'm going to
set this thing about as perfect as I can
I mean I do have the brakes up pretty
high but I just want to show you
what this thing can do
if I give it just
mile if I cast as hard as I can I'm not
going to put my thumb on it
that's pretty good I'll try one more and
I'll cast a little bit harder and see
what it does I'll even turn the brakes
down a little bit turn the brakes down
oh
turn the brakes down to halfway okay
we'll see what that does we'll see how
much of an effect the brakes have I
haven't tried this yet so if this goes
good I'll turn them all the way down for
you guys but I'm expecting maybe a
little bit of a bird's nest here
wow that's not bad I mean actually it
went pretty well and that actually did
go significantly farther too with those
breaks at half halfway so we might uh
we're gonna reel this in and we're gonna
try turning these all the way down and
see what happens I'm expecting a little
bit of a bird's nest
all right so we're going to turn these
brakes all the way down and we're going
to give it our hardest cast and see what
happens
oh there it is there's the bird's nest
well that's a No-No don't turn the
brakes all the way down and cast as hard
as you can
You're Gonna Wanna probably adjust it a
little bit better than that
okay now we have the brakes turned back
down casting with ease get a lot of
distance on it though even with those
brakes halfway I mean that thing really
can get chucked out there which is
pretty impressive but all in all guys I
mean I'd give this real probably uh you
know for Budget setup 120 dollars I'd
say eight out of ten I mean I think Abu
Garcia really has done something here I
mean they made a pretty affordable rod
and reel combo for bait casters and it
does really well because if you guys
have ever fished with a super super
cheap bait caster you know that they can
be kind of a mess to fish with not to
say you don't need some thumb control
with this guy especially if you're gonna
be throwing super light you know super
light stuff you know I have a weight on
my senko I'd probably be a little more
scared to throw it weightless but you
know honestly if you're gonna fish with
a weightless increase you'll probably
use a spinning reel anyway which is why
I threw a weight on it
um but all in all yeah I'd say seven
maybe eight out of ten does really
really good and I think I'll keep this
rod for a long long time as long as it
holds up over the test of time which it
should it's uh it's made it's made from
pretty quality components so I don't see
any issue as to why it won't hold up for
quite a long time
um I'd say if you're looking for you
know a bait caster in that range I'd say
you're pretty safe to go with it I
really really like the white and black I
think it gives it a really cool look
um it's kind of just aesthetically
pleasing and I'd say honestly for 120
bucks this thing competes with the Abu
Garcia Veritas and if you guys want to
check out that video I have done a
product review on that which I'll link
at the top of the video but honestly I
don't see the need to buy it I feel like
for 120 bucks you can get something
pretty similar and spend half as over
half as much so I would definitely give
it a look guys if you did enjoy this
video make sure you like the video and
subscribe to the channel and I'll see
you guys in the next one peace